<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Swaroj</string>
    <string name="submit_details">Submit Details</string>
    <string name="migrant">MIGRANT</string>
    <string name="local">LOCAL</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter name</string>
    <string name="enter_address">Enter address</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter email</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter password</string>
    <string name="log_in">LOG IN</string>
    <string name="register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="register_migrant">Register as MIGRANT</string>
    <string name="register_local">Register as LOCAL</string>
    <string name="prephoneno">+91 xxxxx-xxxxx</string>
    <string name="get_otp">Get OTP</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="enter_last_location">Enter last location</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dashboard_map">Map</string>
    <string name="swaroj_2020_all_rights_reserved">©Swaroj 2020. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="something_s_not_right_restart_app">Something\'s not right. Restart app.</string>
    <string name="click_near_me_to_refresh">Click <b><i>NEAR ME</i></b> to refresh.</string>
    <string name="refresh">refresh</string>
    <string name="a_social_distancing_platform">A social distancing platform</string>
    <string name="no_migrants">No migrant people currently nearby.\n Click <b><i>NEAR ME</i></b> to refresh.</string>
    <string name="some_migrants">Some migrant people currently nearby.\n Click <b><i>NEAR ME</i></b> to refresh.</string>
    <string name="many_migrants">Many migrant people currently nearby.\n Click <b><i>NEAR ME</i></b> to refresh.</string>
    <string name="pp1">
        SWAROJ takes the responsibility of having your personal information very seriously. It uses
your personal information only for only improving the Service. It keeps your personal
information as its own and keeps it confidential. By using the Service, you consent to the
collection and use of information in accordance with this Policy. \n

SWAROJ reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace this Policy by posting
the updated version on the Site. It is your responsibility to check this Policy periodically for
changes. Your continued use of the Service following the posting of any changes to this
Policy constitutes your acceptance of those changes.\n

</string>
<string name="aqquire">ACQUIRING OF INFORMATION\n</string>

    <string name="pp2">
We may acquire the following information about you.
Information (such as your name, telephone number) that you provide while booking on the
application.
Your log-in which is done using your mobile no which is in connection with the account
sign-in process;
Details of any requests or transactions made by you through the Service;
Communications you send to us, for example to report a problem or to submit queries,
concerns, or comments regarding the Service or its content;
Information that you post to the application in the form of comments or contributions to
discussions and IP addresses \n
    </string>
    <string name="personal">USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION\n</string>
    <string name="pp3">

We will use the personal information that you provide for:
Identifying you when you book our service;
Enable us to provide you with the services;
Send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us
    </string>
</resources>
